(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ReGLOSS 3D LIVE Reach the top
2024 09.28 SAT 8 PM(JST)
本日は、ReGLOSS 3Dライブ「Reach the top」にお越しいただき、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for joining us today for the ReGLOSS 3D Live, "Reach the top."
皆様に本公演の注意事項を申し上げます。
We have a few announcements regarding today's performance.
携帯電話の電源は切らずに、パソコン、タブレットなどとの複数窓での視聴をおすすめしております。
Please keep your mobile phones on; we recommend watching across multiple windows on your PC or tablet.
公演中のおしゃべりは大歓迎です！ ぜひコメントして本公演を一緒に盛り上げてください。
Chatting during the show is more than welcome! Please leave comments and let's get hyped together.
公演中の写真撮影も大歓迎です。たくさんスクショして、ハッシュタグ #ReGLOSS3Dライブ でポストしてください。
Taking photos during the show is also welcome. Take plenty of screenshots and post them with the hashtag #ReGLOSS3DLive.
二十歳以上の方に限り、ご自宅内での喫煙、飲酒も可となっております。思う存分お楽しみください。
For those of legal age, smoking and drinking at home is permitted. Please enjoy to your heart's content.
本公演のあとにメンバーシップ限定のライブがございます。ぜひメンバーシップへの参加をお願いいたします。
There will be a membership-exclusive live after this performance. Please consider joining our membership.
それでは……
And now...
開演までしばらくお待ちください！
Please wait a little longer for the show to start!
ReGLOSS 1st Anniversary
Reach the top!
皆様、本日はReGLOSS 3Dライブ「Reach the top」にお越しいただき、誠にありがとうございます。
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you very much for joining us for the ReGLOSS 3D LIVE "Reach the top" today.
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
皆様に本公演の注意事項を申し上げます。
I will now explain the precautions for this performance.
なになに？教えて！
What is it? Tell us!
携帯電話の電源は切らずに...
Without turning off your cell phones...
えっ！？
Eh!?
...パソコン、タブレットなどでの複数窓でのご視聴、お勧め致しております。
...we recommend viewing in multiple windows on a PC, tablet, or similar device.
500窓！ 500窓！？
500 windows! 500 windows!?
えっ？
Eh?
公演中のお喋りは大歓迎です。
Chatting during the performance is most welcome.
やったー！
Yay!
コメントとして本公演を一緒に盛り上げてください！
Please liven up the performance together with your comments!
いぇーい！
Yay!
公演中の写真撮影も大歓迎です。
Taking photos during the performance is also welcome.
やったー！ たくさん撮るぞ！
Yay! I'm going to take lots of photos!
ハッシュタグ #ReGLOSS3Dライブ でポストしてください。
Please post with the hashtag #ReGLOSS3Dライブ.
あと青くんかっこいいとも言ってください。いぇーい！
And also, please say Ao-kun is cool. Yay!
二十歳以上の方に限り、ご自宅内での喫煙、飲酒も可となっております。
Smoking and drinking at home is permitted only for those 20 years of age or older.
思う存分お楽しみください。
Please enjoy to your heart's content.
そして本公演の後に、メンバーシップ限定のライブがございます。
And after this performance, there will be a membership-exclusive live.
なんだって！？
What!?
ぜひメンバーシップへの参加をお願い致します。
Please join the membership by all means.
こちらのメンバーも楽しみ！
I'm looking forward to that as well!
それでは、開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Now, please wait a while until the performance begins.
しばらくお待ちくださーい！
Please wait a while!
ReGLOSS、いくよ！
ReGLOSS, let's go!
漠然としていた　fun
I was vaguely wishing...
欲していた　fun
...for some fun.
日常に違和感
I felt out of place in daily life,
うんざりしていた
I was fed up with it all.
着慣れた　ありきたりな眺め
Gazing at the same old scenes,
理屈を超える変化を求めていた
I was looking for a change beyond logic.
窮屈で退屈な日々の中
Amidst the cramped and boring days,
突然　君は現れた
you suddenly appeared.
全身の細胞　駆け巡るように
Like it's racing through every cell in my body,
走り出した　未完成なストーリー
an unbraked story has begun.
モノクロであった景色が今
The scenery that was once monochrome...
君と出会い　カラフルに彩る　pan-u-wa
...is now colored vibrantly because I met you.
心奪われた　気まぐれな瞬間ハートビート
My heart was stolen by this
capricious Momentary Heartbeat.
エラティックの狭間　もう一人じゃない　煌めく星
In the threshold of the erratic,
I'm no longer alone, my sparkling star.
描く未来予想図は
In the future we envisioned,
同じ夢を引き寄せたいよ
I want to draw in the same dream.
果てしない旅路の向こうで
Beyond the endless journey,
鳴り止まないロマンが待っている
a never-ending romance awaits.
気付いた時にはね
By the time I noticed,
Can't be without you
いつまでも君と一緒なら
If I'm with you forever,
ここから先広がる宇宙
the universe will expand from here.
晴れ渡り空　飛び出して
Jump out into the clear sky,
気分は上々　外行っちゃおう
the mood is just right, let's go out.
既定の苦労は終わりにして
Put an end to the usual hardships,
全て叶え　空を飛ぼう
I'll grant everything, let's fly to the sky.
時計の針が
The hands of the clock...
回り回る
...keep turning and turning.
限られた時の中で
Vividly, within this limited time,
鮮やかに　Dance time
it's dance time.
心奪われた　気まぐれな瞬間ハートビート
My heart was stolen by this
capricious Momentary Heartbeat.
エラティックの狭間　もう一人じゃない　煌めく星
In the threshold of the erratic,
I'm no longer alone, my sparkling star.
描く未来予想図は
In the future we envisioned,
同じ夢を引き寄せたいよ
I want to draw in the same dream.
果てしない旅路の向こうに
Beyond the endless journey,
紛れもない奇跡があるはず
there's a miracle without a doubt.
さよならメランコリー　止められはしないこの衝動
Goodbye melancholy, I can't stop this impulse.
突き進むだけさ　なりふり構わず　Are you ready?
Just keep moving forward without
worrying about appearances, are you ready?
限界は最大　重なる多次元の異次元
The limit is maximum,
multidimensional and infinite.
散りばめた煌めき　夜空みんな聴いて
Spread out the sparkle,
listen to it, everyone in the night sky.
喜びは悲しみの場合分け　分かち合っていこう
Let's share joy and double the sadness.
僕らなら　どこまでも
If it's us, we can go anywhere.
鳴り止まぬ鼓動 かき消すように 弦をはじいて
Strumming the strings as if to drown out
the unceasing heartbeat
一心不乱に叫ぶ午後 割れた爪を眺めてる暇もないよ
An afternoon of shouting in earnest,
no time to look at broken nails
時の流れに飲み込まれたっていい
It's okay to be swallowed by the flow of time
立ちはだかる壁に 向こう側を覗かそう
Let's peek at the other side
of the walls that stand in our way
ぱっと見惑わす 君が気付けばマスターピース
登りつめていけ いただき 努力だけは裏切らない
If you notice the confusion at first glance, it's a masterpiece.
Climb to the top; only effort won't betray you.
巻いてる点と線 目いっぱい 線と線
晴れてるヘッドセット ずっとずっと点光線
Dots and lines scattered, lines and lines to the full.
Headset set up, always and forever, a beam of light.
はぐらかした桃源郷 静かに灯す 青い炎
A red-herring paradise, quietly lighting a blue flame.
多少強引でもご挨拶 じっと見つめて
Even if it's a bit forced, a greeting. Stare intently.
駆けていく 旋律のよう 恋い焦がれて 咲き乱れて
Running like a melody, yearning, blooming in full glory.
失いかけた夢の続きを 紡いでいこう
Let's spin the continuation of the dream we almost lost.
乾いた世界を満たしてメロディ Keep your heart, 一心同体
Fill the parched world, melody. Keep your heart, as one soul.
君と重なりシンメトリー 手繰り寄せ 朝日のほうへ
Symmetry overlapping with you.
Drawing closer, towards the morning sun.
ほんの微妙なニュアンスの違い 絶妙なバランスの塩梅で
Just a slight difference in nuance,
with an exquisite balance of seasoning.
全ての歯車たちは巧妙に噛み合っている
All the gears are cleverly interlocking.
数学より緻密な赤い眼光のパラダイム いつも隣り合わせでドライ
A paradigm of red glint more precise than math,
always dry and side-by-side.
これの果て誰かのナラティブ 新未来も新時代も信じない
今だけを切り開きよう
At the end of this, someone's narrative.
I don't believe in the new future or the new era, let's just carve out the now.
迫る終焉の足音 願い事は叶わなくとも
The sound of the approaching end,
even if my wishes don't come true.
始まりまであと一歩 息を潜めて
Just one step away from the beginning. Hold your breath.
静寂を切り裂いて 宇宙(そら)へ翼羽ばたかせて
Cut through the silence and let your wings flap towards the sky.
待ち望む結末に 瞬きすらできないよ
I can't even blink at the long-awaited ending.
どんな葛藤も緊張もカタストロフィ 前を向いて飛び越えろ
No matter the conflict, tension, or catastrophe,
look ahead and jump over it.
真っ新な余白に秘めた想い もう後戻りはしない
The feelings hidden in the brand-new blank space,
there's no going back now.
駆けていく 旋律のよう 恋い焦がれて 咲き乱れて
Running like a melody, yearning, blooming in full glory.
失いかけた夢の続きを 紡いでいこう
Let's spin the continuation of the dream we almost lost.
乾いた世界を満たしてメロディ Keep your heart, 一心同体
Fill the parched world, melody. Keep your heart, as one soul.
君と重なりシンメトリー 手繰り寄せ 朝日のほうへ
Symmetry overlapping with you.
Drawing closer, towards the morning sun.
イエーイ！
Yeah!
めっちゃ緊張したー！
I was so nervous!
泣きそうなんだけどー
I'm about to cry...
やばいやばい
This is crazy, this is crazy!
トレンド1位だって！
We're #1 on trending!
えー！すごい！嬉しい！
What! Amazing! So happy!
本当にトレンド1位だ！
It's really #1 on trending!
水飲んでおいで。
Go drink some water.
リリカも水飲もう。
Ririka, drink some water too.
僕は僕だけになるよー。
I'll be just me for a moment.
ということで皆さん、お集まりいただきありがとうございます！
So everyone, thank you for coming today!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
よし、みんな集まったからいつものやつ行きますか！
Alright, everyone's back, shall we do the usual thing?
リーチ・ザ・トップ！ We are ReGLOSS!
Reach the top! We are ReGLOSS!
もう一回、もう一回。
One more time, one more time.
リーチ・ザ・トップ！ We are ReGLOSS!
Reach the top! We are ReGLOSS!
じゃあ青から自己紹介お願いします。
Okay, Ao, please introduce yourself first.
はい！可愛い女の子かと思った？ジャジャーン、青くんでした！
ホロライブデバイス、リグロスのボーイッシュ担当、火威青です！
Yes! Did you think I was a cute girl? Ta-da, it's Ao-kun!
I'm Hiodoshi Ao, in charge of the boyish style for Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS!
ドレミファソラシド！ホロライブデバイス所属、リグロスの音楽の友、音乃瀬奏です！
緊張してるけど今日楽しんでいくぞー！
Do-Re-Mi-Fa-So-La-Si-Do! I'm Otonose Kanade,
the music companion of ReGLOSS from Hololive DEV_IS!
I'm nervous, but let's have fun today!
可愛い、ポジティブ、ジーニアス！ホロライブデバイス、リグロスの一条莉々華だよ！
みんなに会えてめっちゃ嬉しい、ありがとね！今日は楽しんでいってください！
Cute, positive, genius! I'm Ichijou Ririka from Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS!
I'm so happy to see everyone, thank you! Please enjoy today!
はい！えー、ホロライブデバイスはリグロスの賑やかしネタ枠...
Yes! Uh, from Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS, the lively comedy segment...
ちゃんと、儒不手一番は、前座見習い儒不手、ら、ら、らでございます！
Indeed, Jufute No. 1 is... opening act apprentice Jufute, Ra-ra-Raden!
はい！ぷんぷんぷん！
Yes! Pun-pun-pun!
ほらデバチカデバチサリゴロツのパンチョ、
Look, the punch of Debachika Debachi Sarigorotsu,
轟はじめでございまーす！
Todoroki Hajime here!
自己紹介も終わりましたが、
Now that introductions are over...
みんな、3Dだー！
Everyone, we're in 3D!
待って待って待って、みんな。2曲歌ったわけですけど。
Wait, wait, wait, everyone. We've sung two songs.
歌った。
We did.
待って、踊ったじゃん。
Wait, we danced too.
踊った踊った。
We did, we did.
もししかして、その振りって...
Could it be, those moves are...
はい！実録、
Yes! Actually,
轟はじめが、えっと、瞬間ハートビートと、
Todoroki Hajime, uh, for 'Shunkan Heartbeat' and...
シンメトリー、サビの振り付け担当しました！
choreographed the chorus for 'Symmetry'!
そして、グロッサーのみんな、
And to all the Glossers out there,
アルバム予約してくれたかな？
did you pre-order the album?
今回のセットリストには、なんと、
This setlist actually includes...
11月リリースのファーストアルバム、
all seven tracks from our first album,
『ReGLOSS』の全楽曲7曲を披露します！
'ReGLOSS,' coming out in November!
半分くらいは初お披露目の曲なので、
About half of them are being performed for the first time,
楽しみにしていてください。
so please look forward to it.
早速『瞬間ハートビート』と『シンメトリー』を披露しましたが、
We just performed 'Shunkan Heartbeat' and 'Symmetry,'
どうだったかな？
but how did you like them?
すごいコメントが...
There are so many comments...
名前も呼んでくれてる。
They're calling out our names, too.
でもね、まだまだ楽しいこと盛りだくさん。
But there's still plenty more fun to come.
これからもいっぱい歌っていくので、
We're going to keep singing a lot more,
みんないっぱい楽しんでいってください！
so everyone, please keep on enjoying yourselves!
あ。
Ah.
もう、しょうがないな。
Ah, geez, I guess I have no choice.
よし、ほい！
Alright, there!
同じ未来を見ていたい
I want to see the same future as you
あの夢手にしたい
I want to reach that dream
それぞれ違った心で 走れ Go!
With our different hearts, run! Go!
みんな！ソロパート始まるよ！
Everyone! The solo part is starting!
ずっと憧れだった曲、聴いてください。
Please listen to the song I've always admired.
Shiny Smily Story！
Shiny Smily Story!
どこ見ても真っ暗な場所に芽生えてた
It sprouted in a place where everywhere was pitch black
ほんの小さな希望にこの瞳奪われた
This tiny hope caught my eyes
不安で揺れる心を上手くチューニングして
Finely tuning my heart that was shaking with anxiety
ほんの小さな勇気を振り絞っていたよ
I was squeezing out just a little bit of courage
諦めの文字 デリートして進む
Deleting the word 'giving up' as I move forward
苦しい時も私は一人じゃないから
Because even in hard times, I'm not alone
だからもっと夢追いかけたい
So I want to chase my dreams even more
ワクワク止まらない
The excitement won't stop
想像を超えていく世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that goes beyond imagination
アクセスしてみたい 後悔なんてさせない
I want to try accessing it, I won't let you regret it
それぞれ違った心で 走れ Go!
With our different hearts, run! Go!
画素の空に輝く眩しい思いは
Dazzling feelings shining in the pixel sky
見たことのない光をリアルに届けるよ
Will deliver a light you've never seen to reality
いつも聞こえるエールはここにキャプチャして
Capturing the cheers I always hear right here
また新しい光を、探したくなるよ
It makes me want to search for a new light again
君の笑顔は保存して進む
Saving your smile as I move forward
悲しい時に見返すよ 力が湧くから
I'll look back at it when I'm sad, it gives me strength
胸を張って夢追いかけたい
I want to chase my dreams with pride
奇跡のストーリー
A miraculous story
一緒に作ろう 終わらない夢を
Let's create an endless dream together
誰一人欠かせない 相まったこの世界
No one is replaceable in this intertwined world
それぞれ違った心で 彩れ
Color it with our different hearts
悲しい時も、寂しい時も...
In sad times, in lonely times...
信じ合えるものがある 忘れずに
There's something we can believe in together, don't forget it
この鼓動を鳴らし続けたい
I want to keep making this heartbeat sound
終わらない世界に 溢れ出すよ
In an unending world, it starts to overflow
笑顔たち
All these smiles
憧れの舞台立ちたい
I want to stand on the stage of my dreams
らしく輝きたい
I want to shine in my own way
時になみだして また笑い合いたい
Sometimes crying, then wanting to laugh together again
同じ未来を見たい
I want to see the same future
あの夢手にしたい
I want to grab that dream
踏み出そう 奇跡の一歩を
Let's take a step toward a miracle
生き切らして夢追いかけたい
I want to chase my dreams with everything I've got
ワクワク止まらない
The excitement won't stop
想像を超えてく 世界に見せてあげる
I'll show the world something beyond imagination
アクセスしてみない?
Why not try accessing it?
後悔なんてここにない
There are no regrets here
それぞれ違った 心で作るわ
We'll create it with our own unique hearts
ミュージック スタート！
Music, start!
3Dライブ 見に来てくれて ありがとう！
Thank you for coming to see my 3D live!
この景色を見られたのは 読者とグロッサ―がいてくれたから
I was able to see this view because my readers and Grossers were here
出会ってくれてありがとう
Thank you for meeting me
愛してるよ！
I love you!
シャンパンシャンパン！
Champagne, Champagne!
皆さん！
Everyone!
ここからは 儒烏風亭らでんのソロパートです！
From here on, it's Juufuutei Raden's solo part!
皆 盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's all get fired up!
皆で行こう 僕たちの夢
Let's go together, towards our dream
ほら広がる世界の先へ
Look, beyond the expanding world
手をかざして未来へ向かう
Holding up our hands, heading for the future
素敵な何かが待ってる
Something wonderful is waiting
鳴らして リンリンロン
Make it ring, ring-ring-ron
手のひらいっぱい
A palm full...
希望胸に扉開けて
Of hope in our hearts, let's open the door
ミュージアム ミュージアム
Museum, Museum
かけがえのない
Irreplaceable...
大切な未来をつなぐ秘密
A secret that connects the precious future
ミュージアム
Museum
ファンタジー
Fantasy...
足りないのは何?
What is missing?
一緒にに見つけようよ
Let's find it together
君にもできるはずさ
I'm sure you can do it too
皆でつなぐ 僕たちの夢
Our dream that connects us all
ほら広がる心のなかへ
Look, into the expanding heart
笑い合えば自信も持てる
If we laugh together, we can gain confidence
素敵な冒険が待ってるよ
A wonderful adventure is waiting
鳴らして リンリンロン
Make it ring, ring-ring-ron
手のひらいっぱい
A palm full...
希望胸に扉開けて
Of hope in our hearts, let's open the door
ミュージアム ミュージアム
Museum, Museum
かけがえのない
Irreplaceable...
大切な未来をつなぐ秘密
A secret that connects the precious future
ミュージアム
Museum
ファンタジー
Fantasy...
足りないのは何?
What is missing?
一緒に見つけようよ
Let's find it together
君にもできるはずさ
I'm sure you can do it too
鳴らして リンリンロン
Make it ring, ring-ring-ron
手のひらいっぱい
A palm full...
希望胸に扉開けて
Of hope in our hearts, let's open the door
ミュージアム ミュージアム
Museum, Museum
かけがえのない
Irreplaceable...
大切な未来をつなぐ秘密
A secret that connects the precious future
ミュージアム
Museum
ファンタジー
Fantasy...
足りないのは何?
What is missing?
一緒に見つけようよ
Let's find it together
君にもできるはずさ
I'm sure you can do it too
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
へっ？なになになに？ここどこ？
Huh? What, what, what? Where am I?
え？ちょっと…なんか手足縛られてんだけど。
Wait, what? My hands and feet are tied up.
どういうこと？何の状況なのこれ？
What's going on? What kind of situation is this?
うわあああ！なんか上からでっかいの降ってきた！
Whoaaa! Something huge fell from above!
で、なんかみんな3Dライブでさ、歌ったり踊ったりさ、華やかな感じだったけど、莉々華は…
Everyone else had such a glamorous 3D live, singing and dancing, but Ririka is...
聞こえますか？
Can you hear me?
ああ、聞こえる。なんか聞き覚えのある声がするわ。なんだ？
Yeah, I hear you. That voice sounds familiar. What's this?
1年ぶりのデスゲーム会場へようこそ。
Welcome to the death game venue for the first time in a year.
これデスゲームか！
This is a death game?!
今からあなたには格付けに挑戦してもらいます。
From now on, I will have you challenge a rating test.
格付け？
A rating test?
1年の間にすっかり弁当飯キャラがついちゃって、
Over the past year, you've completely established a 'convenience store meal' persona,
味音痴だと思われているあなたにチャンスを与えてあげましょう。
and since people think you're a 'tasteless person', I shall give you a chance.
いやいやいや、莉々華は味音痴ではない。
No, no, no, Ririka is not a tasteless person.
安い、早い、旨いを追求した結果があれなだけですから。
That's just the result of me pursuing 'cheap, fast, and delicious'.
味はもうめちゃくちゃ分かりますから。なめないでもらっていいですか？
I understand taste perfectly well. Could you please not underestimate me?
そうですか。
Is that so?
これから目隠しをした状態で「牛肉」の格付けに挑戦してもらいます。
Now, you will challenge a 'beef' rating test while blindfolded.
A・B・Cの肉を食べて値段順に正しく格付けできたらゲームクリアです。
If you eat meats A, B, and C and correctly rank them by price, you clear the game.
なるほど！
I see!
え、手足も縛られた状態で目隠しもしてもらえるご褒美企画ってこと？
Wait, so this is a reward project where I'm blindfolded and tied up?
夢が叶った！
My dream has come true!
今回食べてもらうのは牛ヒレ肉のステーキ。
What you'll be eating this time is beef fillet steak.
1つは200g 1万2千円の高級ステーキ。
One is a high-end steak costing 12,000 yen for 200g.
もう1つは200g 3千円のステーキ。
Another is a steak costing 3,000 yen for 200g.
そしてもう1つは900円の某ステーキ。
And the last one is a 900 yen 'certain steak'.
つまり豚肉です。
In other words, pork.
豚肉！
Pork!
さすがに豚肉と、ね、さすがに豚肉と牛肉の違いぐらい分かると思うんだけどな。
I'm pretty sure I'd at least know the difference between pork and beef.
え、てかさっき1万円を超えるヒレ肉って言ってた？
Wait, did you just say fillet steak costing over 10,000 yen?
なんて幸せなんだ。早く食べたい、早く食べたい！
I'm so happy. I want to eat it now, I want to eat it now!
制限時間は3分。
The time limit is three minutes.
3分！？
Three minutes!?
タイマースタートしてるので目隠し付けちゃいましょうか。
The timer has already started, so shall we put on the blindfold?
待って、もうタイマー始まってんの？早く、早く目隠しして、早く！
Wait, the timer's already started? Quick, blindfold me quickly, hurry!
おーおーおー、前が見えなくなった。
Whoa, I can't see anything now.
怖い、結構怖いな手足縛られて。
It's scary, it's actually quite scary being tied up.
え、でもちょっと待って、3分でね。早く持ってきて、早く早く早く早く早く！
Wait, in three minutes? Bring it quickly, hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry!
1個目。あーむ。
First one. Aah.
うん。ん？ん！美味しい！なんだこれ？
Hmm. Mm? Mm! Delicious! What is this?
ん？なんかピリッとする。
Mm? It's a bit spicy.
んんん…でもこれ牛肉かな？
Mmm... but is this beef?
なんかね、ビーフジャーキーの味するわ。
It kind of tastes like beef jerky.
めちゃくちゃ美味しい。え、次のもください。
It's so delicious. Hey, give me the next one too.
B。あーむ。
B. Aah.
んん！やばい、え？これAとB同じですよね？
Hmm! Oh no, wait? These, A and B, are the same, right?
え、違うもしかして？やばい。え、なんか両方とも旨い。
Wait, are they different? Oh no. They're both delicious.
もうダメかも莉々華。え、じゃCも。ん。
Ririka might be done for. Okay, then C too. Mm.
C。あーむ。
C. Aah.
うん。ん？ん！ん！
Hmm. Mm? Mm! Mm!
Cはなんか家でよく食べる味がする。
C tastes like something I often eat at home.
待ってこれ豚だわ。これ絶対豚。Cは豚だわ。
Wait, this is pork. This is definitely pork. C is pork.
ちょっともう1回AとB順番にお願いします。AとBを。
Could you please give me A and B in order once more? A and B.
あーむ。
Aah.
うん。んんん！なんかもう噛むたびにピリッとした
Hmm. Mmm! Every time I chew, that spicy flavor
なんか風味が口の中に広がってめちゃくちゃ美味しい。
spreads in my mouth and it's so delicious.
あと1分しかないですよ。
You only have one minute left.
ん！やばい、あと1分らしい。B B B B B B B B！
Mm! Oh no, apparently one minute left. B B B B B B B B!
あーむ。
Aah.
うん。なんかとろけるんだよなこれ。
Hmm. This one kind of melts.
美味しいB！食べたい！頂戴！
Delicious B! I want to eat it! Give it to me!
あーむ。
Aah.
んんん！美味しい！幸せだ。
Mmm! Delicious! I'm so happy.
よし！もう時間なさそうだから莉々華分かりました。
Alright! It seems like time's about up, so Ririka has figured it out.
任せてくださいよ。
Leave it to me.
えっと、値段が安い順で、C、A、B。
Um, in order of lowest price: C, A, B.
これで提出です。どや！
This is my submission. Ta-da!
正解！
Correct!
いぇーい！見たか？莉々華はやっぱり味音痴ではないということを
Yay! Did you see that? Ririka is not a tasteless person after all,
これからも料理系VTuberとして手足を縛られ、
and from now on, as a cooking VTuber, while being tied up,
そして目隠しをされながらも美味しい料理を作っていきたいと思います！
and blindfolded, I want to continue making delicious dishes!
ホットドッグ！
Hot dog!
オッケー！ホットドッグ！
Okay! Hot dog!
あ、ごめんなさい、ボタン押しちゃった！
Oh, sorry, I pressed the button!
な、なにやってんだー！
Wh-What was I doing?!
もう、このゲームなんて、こりごりだー！
Ugh, I'm so done with this game!
次は、みんなに仕返ししてやるからなー！
Next time, I'm going to get back at everyone!
どうも、ReGLOSSです！
Hello, we are ReGLOSS!
しびれて、みんな一緒に楽しんでね！
Get excited and let's have fun together!
画面の前でも、声出していこう！
Even in front of your screens, let's hear your voices!
行くぞ！
Let's go!
目くるめく好奇心を忍ばせましょう
Let's harbor our dazzling curiosity
行方、神様さえも知らぬ場所
To a place where even God doesn't know the destination
待ちきれない情熱が
This uncontrollable passion
詰まった今日、肴で例えよう
That fills today, let's compare it to a side dish
寝付きの悪い夜も、途方もないBad newsも
Even sleepless nights and endless bad news
目まぐるしい時代も全部
And even these dizzying times, all of it
豪逆の彼方へ笑い飛ばそう
Let's laugh them off into the distance of arrogance
君だ、ビビディ・バビディ・ブー
It's you, bibbidi-babbidi-boo
行くよ！
Here we go!
SUPER DUPER オートクチュールのシャングリラ
SUPER DUPER, an haute couture Shangri-La
弾き切れるまで踊るのよ
Dance until you've played it all out
誰かが何と言おうと、気にしないリミッター解除
No matter what anyone says, release the limiters without a care
そう、ただ楽しむだけ
That's right, just enjoy it
美しい声を響かせて
Let your beautiful voice ring out
Yeah yeah! Yeah yeah! Yeah yeah! Ah ah
俯いた世界を変えてみせよう
I'll show you I can change this downcast world
Yeah yeah! Yeah yeah! Yeah yeah! SUPER DUPER
焦がし、求めていた、時を経て逆転
Burning with desire, seeking it out, a reversal through time
とっくに決めてる、激アツ覚醒
I've already decided, a super-heated awakening
転生しても、もう一度ここへCome back
Even if I'm reincarnated, I'll come back here again
人生そのものがセンセーショナルな漫画
Life itself is a sensational manga
惹きながら一躍、羽ばたいて鳥になれ
Charming everyone as you take flight, become a bird
一番目指し、走り出せ、地に足付け自由にさあ
Aim for the top, start running, plant your feet and be free
巷を揺らす、大騒ぎ
A huge commotion shaking the streets
浮き足立ったって問題ない
It's fine even if you're restless
ざわついた胸の奥、愛して止まないもの
Deep in my restless heart, the things I love endlessly
疑うことも知らないまま
Without even knowing how to doubt
そう、一世一代、覚悟はできてるよ
Yes, once in a lifetime, I'm prepared
君だ、君だ、未来だ
It's you, it's you, it's the future
SUPER DUPER オートクチュールのシャングリラ
SUPER DUPER, an haute couture Shangri-La
弾き切れるまで踊るのよ
Dance until you've played it all out
誰かが何と言おうと、気にしないリミッター解除
No matter what anyone says, release the limiters without a care
そう、ただ楽しむだけ
That's right, just enjoy it
美しい声を響かせて
Let your beautiful voice ring out
Yeah yeah! Yeah yeah! Yeah yeah! Ah ah
俯いた世界を変えてみせよう
I'll show you I can change this downcast world
Yeah yeah! Yeah yeah! Yeah yeah! SUPER DUPER
一喜一憂も、一語一向さ、注いで、一心同体でいて
Ups and downs, every single word, pour it out, stay as one heart and body
今宵なき、恋したメロディと
Tonight's gone, with the melody I fell in love with
会えなくて、離したレプリカ
Unable to meet, the replica I let go of
名もなき君との境界線を、超え、リフレイン
Crossing the boundary with the nameless you, refrain
やった！
We did it!
SUPER DUPER オートクチュールのシャングリラ
SUPER DUPER, an haute couture Shangri-La
弾き切れるまで踊るのよ
Dance until you've played it all out
誰かが何と言おうと、気にしないリミッター解除
No matter what anyone says, release the limiters without a care
そう、ただ楽しむだけ
That's right, just enjoy it
美しい声を響かせて
Let your beautiful voice ring out
Yeah yeah! Yeah yeah! Yeah yeah! Ah ah
俯いた世界を変えてみせよう
I'll show you I can change this downcast world
Yeah yeah! Yeah yeah! Yeah yeah! SUPER DUPER
いえーい！お疲れ様でしたー！
Yay! Good job everyone!
いやぁ、最後のSUPER DUPER、ちょっと、言っちゃった！
Wow, that last SUPER DUPER, I kind of said it!
ごめんね、ごめんね。かまわよ、かまわよ、全然いいよ！
Sorry, sorry. It's okay, it's okay, no problem at all!
ありがとうございました！ソロパートと、えー、ユニット曲
Thank you very much! You heard the solo parts and, um, the unit song
「SUPER DUPER」聴いていただきましたが、
'SUPER DUPER,' but
青くん、感動したよ、SSS！
Ao-kun, I was moved, SSS!
いや、めっちゃ上手かったよ！凄かったよ！
No, you were really good! It was amazing!
僕、絶対ホロライブに入って3Dお披露目する時は
I had decided that I would definitely sing
絶対歌うって決めてました。
when I joined Hololive and had my 3D debut.
歌わせていただきありがとうございます！
Thank you for letting me sing!
シャンパンも最高だったよ！
The champagne was great too!
いや、あ、それはちょっと、なんか、途中でゴフッてなってた...
Well, uh, that was a little... I kind of choked in the middle...
ちなみにシャンパンコールはオリジナルです！
By the way, the champagne call is an original!
いえーい！で、ね、らでんちゃんのも凄かったよ！
Yay! And, you know, Raden-chan's was amazing too!
今までの集大成的な感じだったね！
It felt like a culmination of everything so far!
はい、そうです。えっと、今回ですね、
Yes, that's right. For this time,
撮影にご協力いただきました、箱根ガラスの森美術館さん、
we received cooperation for the filming from the Hakone Glass Forest Museum,
ポーラ美術館さん、本当にありがとうございました！
and the Pola Museum of Art. Thank you very much!
いえーい！
Yay!
ピチエダンスもめちゃくちゃ可愛かったよ！
The Pichi-e dance was also super cute!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
で、莉々華さん！
And, Ririka-san!
ちょっとオリジナル曲のダンスの、
The dance for our original song...
あれ本当にすごかったです、座ってもらってました！
that was really amazing, I was watching it from the side!
イエーイ！
Yay!
こっちかな？あっちかな？
This way? Or that way?
莉々華下手くそか？
Ririka, are you bad at this?
これが俺たちの莉々華だ！
This is our Ririka for you!
莉々華！
Ririka!
これでこそ莉々華だよ！
That's exactly what makes her Ririka!
最高！
Great!
Amazing!
はい、じゃあちょっとね、次の曲の準備もしましょうか。
Okay, well then, shall we prepare for the next song?
そうだね。
Right.
はい、じゃあマイク取りに。
Alright, let's go get the mics.
次は、あの曲。
Next is that song.
マイク、スタンドマイクですってよ。
The mic... apparently it's a stand mic.
なんですって！
What did you say?!
良い呼吸だ。
Breathe in deep.
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
大丈夫です。
I'm okay.
はい。
Good.
じゃあ、みんなオッケーかな？
Now, is everyone ready?
うん。
Yeah.
それでは次の曲、聴いてください。泡沫メイビー。
Then please listen to our next song. 'Utakata Maybe'.
泡沫メイビー
作詞：OHTORA
作曲：OHTORA / maeshima soshi
編曲：maeshima soshi
Utakata Maybe
Lyrics: OHTORA
Music: OHTORA / maeshima soshi
Arrangement: maeshima soshi
あの日見た夢みたいな
Like a dream I had that day
静けさ
The silence
触れた　本当は　まだ半信半疑
I touched it, but truthfully, I'm still half in doubt
行き違い過ぎたエウレカ
A moment of realization that passed me by
尽きるまでは　覚めない探究心
An inquisitive heart that won't wake up until it runs out
立ち止まれば目の前には
If I stop, right before my eyes
振り返った時の自分がいて
Is the self from when I looked back
小声でささやくシルエット
A silhouette whispering in a low voice
ぼやけて何も聞こえないフレッシュ
A blurry, fresh sound where I can't hear a thing
泡沫メイビー　回れ右今夜分かれ道
Ephemeral Maybe, about-face, tonight is a fork in the road
胸騒ぎメインに　繰り返しサヨナラ溜息
With unease as the main theme, repeating goodbyes and sighs
ほんのちょっとのアイだのテイだの　くすぐったままのテイだの
Just a little bit of 'love' or 'appearances', maintaining that same ticklish appearance
失った過去も少し痛い？　今はまだ見過ごしていたいよ
Does the lost past hurt a little? For now, I still want to keep overlooking it
空が滲んで　まぶた濡らした
The sky blurred and wetted my eyelids
あと一つ　何かが足りないんだ
There's one more thing, something is missing
10円玉みたいなエブリデイ　滑って転んで手の平のヒビ
An everyday life like a 10-yen coin, slipping and falling, cracks in my palms
構いたいのバイタリティ　いつも記憶がアイマイ
The vitality of wanting to be cared for, memories are always vague
へんてつもない日々の欠片
Fragments of unremarkable days
散らばった体裁をして
Putting on a scattered appearance
ずっとそよ風にそそがれていたい
I want to be continually bathed in a gentle breeze
雲隠れした　笑い合いたい
Hidden by the clouds, I want us to laugh together
泡沫メイビー　回れ右今夜分かれ道
Ephemeral Maybe, about-face, tonight is a fork in the road
胸騒ぎメインに　繰り返しサヨナラ溜息
With unease as the main theme, repeating goodbyes and sighs
しびれるような幕開けを　ただ独り待っているんじゃない
I'm not just waiting alone for a thrilling opening
雲と雲の切れ間から　Raise a Light, Shine
From between the clouds, Raise a Light, Shine
もう後ろを振り返らないで　そう呟いたんだ
Don't look back anymore, that's what I whispered
私にとっての大切な曲をアカペラで歌わせていただきます。
I will sing a song that is important to me acapella.
ああ、あなたから愛されることも
Ah, to be loved by you,
必要とされることもない
or even to be needed by you—neither will happen.
そして私はこうして一人
And so, I am here, alone like this.
Departures ～あなたにおくるアイの歌～
Departures ~Anata ni Okuru Ai no Uta~
あの時　あなたはなんて言ったの
What did you say back then?
届かない言葉は宙を舞う
The words that can't reach you dance in the air
わかってるのに　今日もしてしまう
Even though I know, I still find myself today...
叶わぬ願いごとを
...making a wish that won't come true.
離さないで　ぎゅっと
Don't let go, hold me tight
手を握ってて
Hold my hand
あなたと二人　続くと言って
Say that the two of us will go on together
繋いだその手は温かくて
Those hands we held were so warm...
優しかった
...and so kind.
あなたはいつもそうやって私を
You always did that to me...
怒らせて最後に泣かすんだ
...making me angry and then crying in the end.
だけど後になってごめんねと言う
But then later you'd say "I'm sorry"...
その顔好きだった
...I loved that face of yours.
離さないで　ぎゅっと　そう思いきり
Don't let go, hold me tight, with all your might
あなたの腕の中にいたい
I want to be in your arms
二人でおでこを合わせながら
As we press our foreheads together...
眠るの
...and fall asleep.
二度と会えないってことを知ってたの
I knew that we would never meet again.
離さないで　ぎゅっと　あなたが好き
Don't let go, hold me tight, I love you
もう一度だって笑ってくれないの
Won't you even smile for me one more time?
あなたの温もりが消えちゃう前に
Before your warmth disappears...
抱きしめて
Hold me.
LAKI MODE
遠目仰いだ雲の上
Above the clouds I gazed at from afar
ベールに包まれた星待って
Waiting for the stars wrapped in a veil
流れ落ちてきた光にまたがって
Astride the light that came falling down
一緒に浮遊飛行しよう
Let's go on a floating flight together
ルカマスの星たちが嬉々としてステップ刻んで
The stars of Rukamasu lively treading steps
我が物顔でなびくアイソレーション　きらめき噛む絶対零度
Isolation fluttering as if it owns the place, biting the sparkle, absolute zero
冴えない夢にはおあいそ
A courtesy for the dull dreams
花咲く笑顔が似合いそう
A blooming smile would surely suit you
色褪せぬパラティソ踊ろうよ Under the starlight
Let's dance in the unfading paradise, under the starlight
流れに身を委ねて
Entrusting your body to the flow
...ちゃちゃ酔わせてよ LAKI MODE
...cha-cha, let me get drunk, LAKI MODE
キミだけのプレイリスト
Your very own playlist
マイフロー耳元まで運ぶよ
My flow, I'll carry it to your ears
Don't be shy, emotion
Don't be shy, LAKI MODE
闇を照らすオーロラ
Aurora that lights up the darkness
言葉いらずのオリマー
No need for words, All in my
踊ってたいずっと
I want to keep dancing forever
またとないこの日を
This one-of-a-kind day
降り注ぐプラズマ
Pouring plasma
キミがいればプラスワン
If you're here, it's a plus one
色濃く映そう VIVIDなハイライト
Let's show it vividly, VIVID highlights
やみつきになる Dance Dance
It's addictive, Dance Dance
ハイになるまで I I
Until we're high, I I
寝ても覚めても 華やぐトワイライト
Asleep or awake, the twilight flourishes
きらめいたら Nice Nice
If it sparkles, Nice Nice
もっと光 I Ice
More light, I Ice
感性の奇劇にふっと酔いしれた
Suddenly intoxicated by the comedy of sensibility
そんな野蛮な季節は通り過ぎた
That barbaric season has passed
みんなホトほと知らずなぐらいが一番ちょうどいい
It's just right when everyone is somewhat oblivious
甘めにフィルタかけて強気のヒビ
Apply a sweet filter and have confident days
続、バラバラの sense of unity
Continuation, a scattered sense of unity
ワンランク上果たす現状維持
Maintaining the status quo while going up a level
隣り合わせ反応するメロディ
Melodies reacting side-by-side
まるで狂信的、キミの殿堂入り
Like a fanatic, inducted into your Hall of Fame
染まる心、瞳めがけ覚醒
A dyed heart, awakening towards the eyes
バース後の精度も超え
Exceeding even the precision after the verse
沸き余った距離さえも Kilometers
Even the boiling distance is Kilometers
天使みたく舞い踊るクリオーネ
Dancing like an angel, Clione
夢中になっていた頃には
By the time I was engrossed
時は行方を眩ませた
Time had vanished
幸せ運ぶ水星が
The comet bringing happiness
オーバーフロー満たしていく世界中
Filling the world with an overflow
Don't be shy, emotion
Don't be shy, LAKI MODE
闇を照らすオーロラ
Aurora that lights up the darkness
言葉いらずのオリマー
No need for words, All in my
踊ってたいずっと
I want to keep dancing forever
またとないこの日を
This one-of-a-kind day
降り注ぐプラズマ
Pouring plasma
キミがいればプラスワン
If you're here, it's a plus one
色濃く映そう VIVIDなハイライト
Let's show it vividly, VIVID highlights
やみつきになる Dance Dance
It's addictive, Dance Dance
ハイになるまで I I
Until we're high, I I
寝ても覚めても 華やぐトワイライト
Asleep or awake, the twilight flourishes
きらめいたら Nice Nice
If it sparkles, Nice Nice
もっと光 I Ice
More light, I Ice
あ、待って
Ah, wait
Stay up she said 立たせて
Stay up she said, let me stand
死に腐れた態度じゃ不合格です
A dead, rotten attitude is a failing grade
不幸中の幸いは飽きてしまうわ
I'll get tired of the silver lining in misfortune
BANDAGE
作詞・作曲：Ayumu Imazu
Lyrics/Composition: Ayumu Imazu
Get up 目を覚まして
Get up, open your eyes
いい加減ななりに黙って頷いてちゃ
Just shut up and keep nodding in your haphazard way
Non non non のびしろがないわ
Non-non-non, there's no room for growth
I got 1 2 3 4 5 6 のまま 稚拙でいいからまとまらず I want to
I got 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6 as it is, it's fine to be childish, without a plan, I want to
Falling out falling out away 追いかける yesterday
Falling out, falling out away, chasing yesterday
決める覚悟 迷いは捨て
The resolution to decide, discard hesitation
風が止まっても研ぎ澄ませ
Even if the wind stops, sharpen up
駆け引きなんていらない say
I don't need any bargaining, say
What you wanna say
指名通りの希望はブルー
The hope as requested is blue
痛みを感じて研ぎ澄ませ
Feel the pain and sharpen yourself
古びたバンデージはいらない
I don't need an old bandage
Do what you want to do
狙って 情けないね
Aiming, how pathetic
言い訳ばかり conversation も勘弁
I've had enough of conversations full of excuses
躓くの恐れちゃどこも行けないわ
If you're afraid of stumbling, you won't go anywhere
Stand up 今日はなんとなく
Stand up, today somehow
牙を見せれば見させられる Nightmare
If I show my fangs, I'm forced to see a nightmare
無感情になれるなら教えて頂戴
If I can become emotionless, please tell me how
Tell me A B C D H とかの合言葉 絞り出して I want to
Tell me A, B, C, D, H etc passwords, squeezing them out, I want to
Falling out falling out away 追いかける one more day
Falling out, falling out away, chasing one more day
決める覚悟 迷いは捨て
The resolution to decide, discard hesitation
風が止まっても研ぎ澄ませ
Even if the wind stops, sharpen up
駆け引きなんていらない say
I don't need any bargaining, say
What you wanna say
指名通りの希望はブルー
The hope as requested is blue
痛みを感じて研ぎ澄ませ
Feel the pain and sharpen yourself
古びたバンデージはいらない
I don't need an old bandage
Do what you want to do
また見て見ぬふりの繰り返し
Again, repeating pretending not to see
ズタボロな心を
A tattered heart
誰かのせいだとしたって何も変わりはしない
Even if it's someone's fault, nothing will change
ほっぺをくすぐっちまうかさぶたに
Tickling scabs on my cheeks,
いつかは剥がれ落ちて
They'll eventually peel off.
そりゃそう　そりゃそう
That's right, that's right.
選んだのさ　自分次第でしょう
You chose it, so it's up to you, right?
決める覚悟　迷いは捨て
Prepared to decide, casting away hesitation,
風を食らう　辿る道
Facing the wind, on the path I walk.
駆け引きなんていらないぜ
No need for bargaining or tactics.
What you wanna say?
優越なマンデー　気分はブルー
Superior Monday, feeling blue,
痛みを噛んで　削ぎ落とす
Chewing on the pain, scraping it away.
古びたバンドエイドいらない　Do what you wanna do
Don't need an old bandage, do what you wanna do.
イエーイ！次の曲は「bvdiz」です！
Yay! Our next song is 'bvdiz'!
イエーイ！みんな！盛り上がってるかーい！
Yay! Everyone! Are you pumped up?!
サンキュー！ぜひ！大きな手拍子を！
Thank you! Please! Give us a big round of applause!
タップもたくさん使ってください！行くぞー！
Use lots of taps too! Here we go!
ドキドキ　最高　Everybody
Thumping hearts, the best, everybody!
Easy Breezy　歌い出せばFavorite
Easy breezy, once you start singing, it's a favorite!
ドキドキ　このままでいたいよね
Thumping hearts, want to stay like this.
Easy Breezy　踊ろうよEverybody
Easy breezy, let's dance, everybody!
それそれ重なったガチ
Hey hey, stacked up for real,
マイナスのプラスになり
Turning minus into plus.
笑えればフリーダムだって価値観
Values that say if you can laugh, you're free.
ドキマギの一発から始まる
Starting from a single flustered moment.
愉快な仲間　景色はバイマイサイド
Funny friends, scenery by my side.
もっと放ちたい　ときにバカ騒ぎ
Want to let loose more, fooling around sometimes.
運命共同体
Sharing a common destiny,
伝染してゆく愛なら
If it's love that spreads...
分かち合えるエンパシー　共に目指すわ
Empathy we can share, let's aim together...
虹の向こうへ
Beyond the rainbow!
絶対絶対絶対絶対的キラチュン
A definitely, definitely, definitely killer tune!
今は自由気まま水色つのユニバース
Now free-spirited, a light-blue horned universe.
Reload Reload Reload 進化するシナプス
Reload, reload, reload, evolving synapses.
限界突破　引き付けるミラコ
Breaking limits, drawing in miracles.
わあ皆さん！手拍子叩いてくれてありがとうね！
Wow, everyone! Thank you for clapping along!
次は、みんなで一緒にワイパーをしていくよ！
Next, let's all do the windshield wiper motion together!
ドキドキ　最高　Everybody
Thumping hearts, the best, everybody!
Easy Breezy　歌い出せばFavorite
Easy breezy, once you start singing, it's a favorite!
ドキドキ　このままでいたいよね
Thumping hearts, want to stay like this.
Easy Breezy　踊ろうよEverybody
Easy breezy, let's dance, everybody!
一人募ればまた一人も一緒に会いたくなる気持ち
The feeling of missing someone more as more people gather.
片隅のモノローグも繋がるプロローグ
A monologue in the corner connects to a prologue.
知る日があった夢のストーリー　みんなといる空間がエクスタシー
A dream story from a day I remember, ecstasy being with you all.
共感するかけがえないメモリー　一緒に無我夢中に掴みとるネクストステージ
Invaluable memories we share, grabbing the next stage together frantically.
運命共同体
Sharing a common destiny,
伝染してゆく愛なら
If it's love that spreads...
分かち合えるエンパシー　共に目指すわ
Empathy we can share, let's aim together...
虹の向こうへ
Beyond the rainbow!
絶対絶対絶対絶対的キラチュン
A definitely, definitely, definitely killer tune!
今は自由気まま水色つのユニバース
Now free-spirited, a light-blue horned universe.
Reload Reload Reload 進化するシナプス
Reload, reload, reload, evolving synapses.
限界突破　引き付けるミラコ
Breaking limits, drawing in miracles.
ドキドキ　最高　Everybody
Thumping hearts, the best, everybody!
Easy Breezy　歌い出せばFavorite
Easy breezy, once you start singing, it's a favorite!
ドキドキ　このままでいたいよね
Thumping hearts, want to stay like this.
Easy Breezy　踊ろうよEverybody
Easy breezy, let's dance, everybody!
イエーイ！
Yay!
いい感じだったね！
That felt good!
やっちゃった！
We did it!
一気に行きおわったね。ソロパートからね、
We finished them all in one go. From the solo parts,
2人の曲、それからbvdizもありましたが、
to the duet, and then bvdiz...
奏のアカペラ痺れたよー！
Kanade's a cappella gave me chills!
やばいー！本当によかった！
Oh man! It was so good!
泣きそう...
I'm gonna cry...
めちゃめちゃよかったよ！
It was absolutely wonderful!
泣きました。
I cried.
頑張ったー。
I did my best.
最高だったよ！
It was the best!
嬉しいです...
I'm so happy...
動きがうるさい。
You're moving too much.
ごめんなさーい。
Sorry!
そんなこと言う番長もさ、めちゃくちゃダンスかっこよかったじゃんね！
But you, Bancho, your dance was super cool too!
すごかった！
It was amazing!
さすがのダンス柱！
As expected of the pillar of dance!
ありがとねー！
Thanks!
ダンス番長。
Dance Bancho.
レベルがちげえぞ！
The level is different!
俺めっちゃ好き。
I really like it.
腰で？あ！これ好き！これ！
The hips? Ah! I like this! This!
ほら。
See.
私もここ、ここ好き！なんかこういうやつ。
I like this part, this part too! Like this kind of thing.
それ違う番長... ブブブブ。
That's a different Bancho... Vroom vroom.
あ、これこれ。違いました。
Ah, this, this. My bad.
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
で、みんなでね、bvdizも歌って。
And then we all sang bvdiz together.
楽しかったにゃー、みんなで。
It was so fun, everyone!
最高！
Awesome!
なんか、楽しめる曲だったよね、めっちゃ。
It was a really enjoyable song.
そうだね。
True.
すごいもう、コメント欄もみんなすごい！
Wow, the comment section is going crazy too!
「奏」とか「番長」とか「梨花」とか「青くん」とか「らでん」とか、みんな！
Kanade, Bancho, Ririka, Ao-kun, Raden... Everyone!
ねって...
They're...
触ってくれてる！
...touching us!
「きのこ」って言ってんの見えて草。
Lol, I see people calling us mushrooms.
分かんないよ、ワンチャンこっちがきのこかも。
You never know, maybe I'm the mushroom.
見て、この帽子。
Look at this hat.
あ、確かに。おい、やめろ！
Ah, true. Hey, stop it!
エノキ！そっちで...
Enoki! Over there...
轟エノキ！
...Todoroki Enoki!
エノキ！エノキじゃないもん！
Enoki! I'm not an Enoki!
美味しそう！
Looks delicious!
え、ちょっとさ、せっかくだからさ、
Wait, since we're here,
みんなさ、クルクルって回転してさ、
let's all spin around
後ろも見てもらおうよ。
and show them our backs too.
いいじゃん！ね！行くよ！
Sounds good! Right! Here we go!
あ、もう回ってた。もう回っちゃった。
Oh, I was already spinning. I already spun.
Yeah! 腹よ！
Yeah! Look at my belly!
こんな感じになってまーす。
This is what it looks like.
いいね！
Nice!
Yeah! ありがとう皆さん！
Yeah! Thank you everyone!
はい、というわけで、残すところあと一曲なんですが...
Alright, and so, there's only one song left...
まだ来たばっかり！
We just got here!
終わった後ですね、
After this is over,
終わった後 21時30分から、
from 21:30,
ReGLOSS 公式チャンネルのメンバーシップ限定で、
on the ReGLOSS official channel membership,
アンコールライブがありますので！
we'll have an encore live!
見たい方は今のうちに、
If you want to watch,
メンバーシップの登録をぜひお願いいたします！
please register for membership now!
お願いします！
Please do!
何やってんだ？
What are you doing?
ちょっと最近、一奏ちゃんのケツばっかりずっと触ってくから...
Lately I've been touching Hajime-chan's butt all the time...
ちょっと待って待って待って！
Wait, wait, wait!
まだあるから！
There's more!
はい、どうぞ。
Yes, go ahead.
私たちのチャンネルのメンバーシップ、
On our individual channel memberships,
私たち個人のですね、チャンネルのメンバーシップでは、
on our personal channel memberships,
推しカメラ配信もございますので、
we have 'oshi-cam' streams,
ぜひ6窓で見ていただければと思います。
so please watch using 6 windows.
よろしくお願いします！
We'd appreciate it!
お願いします！そして、アンコールライブは...
Please do! And the encore live...
このね、今立ってるアリーナじゃない、別のステージ！
...isn't in this arena, but on a different stage!
お！どこ？
Oh! Where?
私たちにゆかりのあるところと言えば...
If you talk about a place we have a connection to...
俺んち！俺んち！俺んち！俺んち！
My house! My house! My house! My house!
まだ待って！
Wait a second!
着替えて、ソロパートの時の衣装での配信となります。
We'll change into our solo outfits for the stream.
裏話とか感想なんかもちょっとゆっくりね、
We'll have time to talk about behind-the-scenes stories
話す時間もあるかなといったところでございますので、
and our thoughts in a relaxed way,
楽しみに待っていてください。
so please look forward to it.
ここで告知情報になります。奏、よろしく！
Now for some announcements. Kanade, if you please!
はい！1stアルバム...
Yes! Our 1st album...
『REGLOSS』、2024年11月6日に発売される、
'REGLOSS', releasing on November 6, 2024,
私たちの 1stアルバム『REGLOSS』が、
our 1st album 'REGLOSS'
絶賛予約受付中です！
is now open for pre-orders!
全国流通盤は初回プレス限定封入特典として、
The distribution version includes a first-press bonus,
ランダムミニカードが1枚入っているのですが、
which is one random mini-card,
ミニカードの絵柄はこちらとなっております！
and the card designs are these!
こちらです！ジャジャン！
Here they are! Ta-da!
可愛いー！
So cute!
各販売店にてお買い求めいただけますので、
They're available at various retailers,
詳細は各販売店さんのサイトをご確認ください。
so please check their websites for details.
うん！
Yep!
さらに！ホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップにて、
Furthermore! At the Hololive Production Official Shop,
通常盤の販売が決定いたしました！
the standard edition will also be available!
イェーイ！
Yay!
こちらは特典で、アニャ... アナザージャケット！
The bonus is Anya... Another jacket!
アニャ？アニャ？アナザージャケット？
Anya? Anya? Another jacket?
本日21時より販売開始となりますので、
Sales start today at 21:00,
詳細は販売ページをご確認ください。そして！
so please check the sales page. And!
はい、僕たちの 3Dアクリルスタンドが出ます！
Yes, our 3D acrylic stands are coming out!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ぜひ5人並べて飾ってください。こんな感じで、
Please display all 5 of us. Like this,
ポンポンポンポンってね。はい。
pop, pop, pop, pop. Yes.
さらに今回の 3Dライブを記念して、グッズが販売されます！
Also, goods to commemorate this 3D live are on sale!
可愛いー！
So cute!
まずはこちら！
First, this!
僕たち5人の手書きのコメントがプリントされた、
A ribbon strap with handwritten comments
リボンタイプのストラップです。
from the five of us.
そしてこちら！
And this!
アクリルフォトフレームと 5人の複製箔押しサイン入りのブロマイドです。
An acrylic photo frame and signed bromide.
以上！すげー噛まなかった！
That's it! I didn't stumble at all!
イェーイ！さすが！
Yay! As expected!
公式オンラインショップで 21時からお求めいただけます。
Available from 21:00 at the official online shop.
でもですね皆さん、今回は数量限定などではないので、
But everyone, these aren't limited in quantity,
皆さん焦らずに最後までこのライブを見てから買ってくださいね。
so please watch until the end before buying.
よろしくプリンセス。そして！
Thanks, princess. And!
9月27日より『REGLOSS』活動1周年記念ボイスが、
Since Sept 27th, our 1st anniversary voices
絶賛発売中です！
have been on sale!
イェーイ！かっこいー！
Yay! So cool!
結成当時の様子を描いたボイスドラマと、
Please enjoy the voice drama of our formation
ボイスメッセージ風シチュエーションボイスをぜひぜひお楽しみください。
and the situation voices.
はい、そして 10月10日に、
Alright, and on October 10th,
3Dライブ振り返りの 3D配信を実施します！やったー！
we'll have a 3D stream to look back on this live! Yay!
おー！聞いてないぞ！聞いてないぞ！何だって？
Oh! We didn't hear about this! What?
次回の 3D配信、10月10日にお会いいたしましょう。
Let's meet at the next 3D stream on Oct 10th.
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
というわけで告知盛りだくさんだったんですけど、
And so, that was a lot of announcements, but...
まだね、皆さん、最後の一曲聞いてないでしょ？
...you haven't heard the last song yet, have you?
聞いてないよ！最後の一曲！
We haven't! The last song!
こないだリリースした新曲、聞きたいよね？
You want to hear the new song we just released, right?
そうだよね！聞きたい！
Right! We want to hear it!
よし、じゃあみんなで一列に付いて、
Alright, then let's get in a line
最後の曲行こう！オー！
and go for the last song! Oh!
フィーリンググラデーション
作詞: OHTORA 作曲: OHTORA / maeshima soshi 編曲: maeshima soshi
Feeling Gradation
Lyrics: OHTORA Comp: OHTORA / maeshima soshi Arr: maeshima soshi
Ah—
My hearts doors get in a mid 紐解いた真情
My hearts doors get in a mid, unraveled my true feelings.
染まり変わりゆくShowtime
The showtime is changing colors,
全然悪くないImagination
a not-so-bad imagination.
誓いの光は晴れ渡って
The light of the vow clears up,
悲しみに別れを告げる
and says goodbye to sadness.
酸いも甘いも宙に放り出して
Throwing the ups and downs into the air,
滲む空インクは薔薇色
the bleeding ink in the sky is rose-colored.
どれだけ格好つけようとしても
No matter how much I try to act cool,
君がいなければ何の意味もない
it means nothing without you.
擦り傷すらつかない嘘
A lie that doesn't even leave a scratch,
針の落ちないレコードさ
a record that never skips.
朝靄と頼りない風背にして
With the morning mist and the unreliable wind at our backs,
Come on let's roll
颯爽と吹き荒れる向かい風にも心
Even in the headwind blowing gallantly, let my heart...
靡かせて
...flutter.
飛び乗って to the future
Jump on to the future!
フライングしたってオーライ restart line hey
Even if we get a head start, it's alright! Restart line, hey!
ときめいてしまえば
Once our hearts start to throb,
瞬く間に広がる開放区
a liberated zone will open up in an instant.
ひとつひとつ全てがパノラマ
Every single thing is a panorama,
待ちわびた Daybreak restart line hey
the long-awaited Daybreak restart line, hey!
変わりゆく色とりどりのパノラマ
A panorama of changing colors,
満ち溢れる Feeling Gradation
overflowing with Feeling Gradation.
始まりのその時が来た
The time of the beginning has come.
Nothing's impossible
紛し紛し欺瞞世界
A world of deceit and confusion.
この先はまだ誰も知らない世界
Beyond this is a world no one knows yet.
ボカしてるだけじゃ味気ない
Just blurring things is boring,
リアルタイムで通じ合って
let's connect in real time.
振り子に駆けろMotion
Swing like a pendulum, Motion,
後の祭りでもアイドントマインド
even if it's too late, I don't mind.
大胆不敵なSituation
A bold situation,
行けるところまで行ってみたい
I want to go as far as I can.
選択肢いらない Get far away
I don't need choices, get far away.
共に声を鳴らせ
Let's make our voices ring out together.
素肌を貫くような真っ直ぐな痛みが
Even if a straightforward pain that pierces the skin...
伴っても
...accompanies us,
その仲間たちと最果てまで
with those friends, to the very end,
Keep running to the end
飛び乗って to the future
Jump on to the future!
フライングしたってオーライ restart line hey
Even if we get a head start, it's alright! Restart line, hey!
ときめいてしまえば
Once our hearts start to throb,
瞬く間に広がる開放区
a liberated zone will open up in an instant.
ひとつひとつ全てがパノラマ
Every single thing is a panorama,
待ちわびた Daybreak restart line hey
the long-awaited Daybreak restart line, hey!
変わりゆく色とりどりのパノラマ
A panorama of changing colors,
満ち溢れる Feeling Gradation
overflowing with Feeling Gradation.
You raise me up 飛び乗って
You raise me up, jump on!
恐れるものはない restart line hey
There's nothing to fear! Restart line, hey!
綺麗な朝焼けが
The beautiful morning glow...
透明な明日を照らすよ
...will illuminate a transparent tomorrow.
Restart line hey
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
あっという間でしたね！
It was over in a flash, wasn't it?
声も出た！
My voice came out too!
最高だった！
It was the best!
最高のみんな！
The best everyone!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
はっしゅたぐ いっぱい呟いて！
Tweet a lot using the hashtag!
待ってるよ！
We're waiting for you!
最後にあれで締めましょう！
Lastly, let's wrap it up with that!
はい！
Yes!
行くよ！ Reach the top! We are...
Here we go! Reach the top! We are...
ReGLOSS!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
またねー！
See you!
大好きだよ！
I love you!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
ReGLOSS 3D LIVE Reach the top
Ririkaより あなたがいたからここまでこれた！！大好きっ♡
From Ririka: I was able to come this far because you were here!! I love you! ♡
やっとキミに会えた！！らぶっ♡
I finally got to meet you!! Love! ♡
ReGLOSS最高ッ！！！
ReGLOSS is the best!!!
ただただうれしい 本当にありがとう 青
I'm just so happy. Thank you so much. - Ao
この仲間なら最高までいける！ついてきて！！ 奏
With these friends, we can go to the very top! Follow me!! - Kanade